In order to implement
linear regression
> 为了实现线性回归
the first key step is first to
> 第一个关键步骤是首先
define something called
a cost function.
> 定义一个称为成本函数的东西。
This is something we'll
build in this video,
> 这是我们将在本视频中构建的东西，
and the cost function
will tell us how well
> 成本函数将告诉我们模型的表现如何
the model is doing so that
> 模型的表现如何
we can try to get
it to do better.
> 我们可以尝试让它做得更好。
Let's look at what this means.
> 让我们看看这意味着什么。
Recall that you have a
training set that contains
> 回想一下，你有一个包含
input features x and
output targets y.
> 输入特征x和输出目标y的训练集。
The model you're going to
use to fit this training set
> 你要用来拟合这个训练集的模型
is this linear function f_w,
> 是这个线性函数f_w，
b of x equals to
w times x plus b.
> b of x等于w乘以x加上b。
To introduce a little bit
more terminology the w
> 为了引入更多术语，w
and b are called the
parameters of the model.
> 和b被称为模型的参数。
In machine learning
parameters of the model are
> 在机器学习中，模型的参数是
the variables you
can adjust during
> 您可以在训练中调整的变量
training in order to
improve the model.
> 以改进模型。
Sometimes you also hear
the parameters w and b
> 有时你也会听到参数w和b
referred to as coefficients
or as weights.
> 被称为系数或权重。
Now let's take a look at what
> 现在让我们看看这些参数w和b
these parameters w and b do.
> 做了什么。
Depending on the values
you've chosen for w and
> 根据您为w和b选择的值
b you get a different
function f of x,
> b，您会得到一个不同的函数f of x，
which generates a different
line on the graph.
> 这在图表上生成不同的线。
Remember that we
can write f of x as
> 记住我们可以将f of x写成
a shorthand for f_w, b of x.
> f_w，b of x的简写。
We're going to take
a look at some plots
> 我们将看一些图表
of f of x on a chart.
> f of x在图表上。
Maybe you're already familiar
> 也许你已经熟悉了
with drawing lines on charts,
> 在图表上画线，
but even if this is
a review for you,
> 但即使这对你来说是一个复习，
I hope this will help
you build intuition
> 我希望这能帮助你建立直觉
on how w and b the parameters
> 关于参数w和b如何
determine f. When w is equal
to 0 and b is equal to 1.5,
> 确定f。当w等于0，b等于1.5，
then f looks like
this horizontal line.
> 那么f看起来像这条水平线。
In this case, the function
f of x is 0 times x
> 在这种情况下，函数f of x是0乘以x
plus 1.5 so f is always
a constant value.
> 加1.5，所以f总是一个常数值。
It always predicts 1.5 for
> 它总是预测1.5
the estimated value of y.
Y hat is always equal to b
> y的估计值。Y hat总是等于b
and here b is also called
> 这里的b也被称为
the y intercept because
that's where it
> y截距，因为那是它
crosses the vertical axis or
the y axis on this graph.
> 在这个图表上穿过垂直轴或y轴。
As a second example,
> 作为第二个例子，
if w is 0.5 and b is equal 0,
> 如果w是0.5，b等于0，
then f of x is 0.5 times x.
> 那么f of x是0.5乘以x。
When x is 0,
> 当x等于0，
the prediction is also 0,
> 预测也是0，
and when x is 2,
> 当x等于2，
then the prediction is
0.5 times 2, which is 1.
> 那么预测是0.5乘以2，即1。
You get a line that looks
like this and notice that
> 你得到一条看起来像这样的线，并注意
the slope is 0.5 divided by 1.
> 斜率是0.5除以1。
The value of w
gives you the slope
> w的值给出了斜率
of the line, which is 0.5.
> 线的斜率，即0.5。
Finally, if w equals
0.5 and b equals 1,
> 最后，如果w等于0.5，b等于1，
then f of x is 0.5 times
x plus 1 and when x is 0,
> 那么f of x是0.5乘以x加1，当x等于0，
then f of x equals b,
> 那么f of x等于b，
which is 1 so the
line intersects
> 即1，所以线与
the vertical axis at
b, the y intercept.
> 垂直轴相交在b，y截距。
Also when x is 2,
> 当x等于2，
then f of x is 2,
> 那么f of x是2，
so the line looks like this.
> 所以线看起来像这样。
Again, this slope
is 0.5 divided by
> 再次，这个斜率是0.5除以
1 so the value of w gives
you the slope which is 0.5.
> 1，所以w的值给出了斜率，即0.5。
Recall that you have
> 回想一下，你有
a training set like
the one shown here.
> 一个像这样的训练集。
With linear regression,
> 使用线性回归，
what you want to do is to choose
> 你想做的是选择
values for the parameters w and
> 参数w和b的值
b so that the straight
line you get from
> 使得从
the function f somehow
fits the data well.
> 函数f得到的直线与数据很好地契合。
Like maybe this line shown here.
> 就像这里显示的线一样。
When I see that the line
fits the data visually,
> 当我看到线与数据视觉上契合时，
you can think of this
to mean that the line
> 你可以认为这意味着线
defined by f is roughly passing
> 由f定义的大致通过
through or somewhere close
to the training examples
> 通过或接近训练示例的线
as compared to other
possible lines
> 与其他可能的线相比
that are not as close
to these points.
> 不如这些点接近。
Just to remind you
of some notation,
> 只是提醒你一些符号，
a training example
like this point
> 一个像这个点的训练示例
here is defined by
x superscript i,
> 这里由x上标i定义，
y superscript i where
y is the target.
> y上标i，其中y是目标。
For a given input x^i,
> 对于给定的输入x^i，
the function f also makes
a predictive value for
> 函数f还为
y and a value that
it predicts to
> y做出预测的值
y is y hat i shown here.
> y是这里显示的y hat i。
For our choice of a model f
of x^i is w times x^i plus b.
> 对于我们选择的模型f of x^i是w乘以x^i加上b。
Stated differently,
the prediction y hat i
> 换句话说，预测y hat i
is f of wb of x^i where
> 是f of wb of x^i，其中
for the model we're using f
> 对于我们使用的模型f
of x^i is equal to wx^i plus b.
> of x^i等于wx^i加b。
Now the question is how
do you find values for
> 现在的问题是如何找到
w and b so that the
prediction y hat i is
> w和b的值，使得预测y hat i
close to the true target y^i for
> 接近真实目标y^i
many or maybe all training
examples x^i, y^i.
> 许多或可能所有训练示例x^i，y^i。
To answer that question,
> 为了回答这个问题，
let's first take
a look at how to
> 让我们首先看一下如何
measure how well a line
fits the training data.
> 测量一条线如何适应训练数据。
To do that, we're going to
construct a cost function.
> 为此，我们将构建一个成本函数。
The cost function takes the
prediction y hat and compares
> 成本函数接受预测y hat并比较
it to the target y by
taking y hat minus y.
> 它与目标y，通过y hat减y。
This difference is
called the error,
> 这个差异被称为错误，
we're measuring how far off to
> 我们正在测量多远
prediction is from the target.
> 预测与目标的差距。
Next, let's computes the
square of this error.
> 接下来，让我们计算这个错误的平方。
Also, we're going to want
to compute this term for
> 此外，我们还要计算这个术语
different training examples
i in the training set.
> 训练集中不同的训练示例i。
When measuring the error,
> 在测量错误时，
for example i,
> 例如i，
we'll compute this
squared error term.
> 我们将计算这个平方误差项。
Finally, we want to measure
> 最后，我们想要测量
the error across the
entire training set.
> 整个训练集的错误。
In particular, let's sum up
the squared errors like this.
> 特别是，让我们这样总结平方误差。
We'll sum from i equals 1,2,
> 我们将从i等于1,2开始求和，
3 all the way up to
> 3一直到
m and remember that m is the
number of training examples,
> m，记住m是训练示例的数量，
which is 47 for this dataset.
> 对于这个数据集，这是47。
Notice that if we have more
training examples m is
> 请注意，如果我们有更多的训练示例m
larger and your cost function
> 更大，你的成本函数
will calculate a bigger number.
> 将计算一个更大的数字。
This is summing
over more examples.
> 这是对更多示例求和。
To build a cost function that
> 要构建一个成本函数
doesn't automatically get bigger
> 不会自动变得更大
as the training set size
gets larger by convention,
> 随着训练集大小的增加而变大，按照惯例，
we will compute the average
squared error instead of
> 我们将计算平均平方误差而不是
the total squared
error and we do
> 总平方误差，我们这样做
that by dividing by m like this.
> 通过这样做来除以m。
We're nearly there.
Just one last thing.
> 我们快到了。最后一件事。
By convention,
> 按照惯例，
the cost function that
machine learning people use
> 机器学习人员使用的成本函数
actually divides by 2 times
m. The extra division
> 实际上除以2乘以m。额外的除法
by 2 is just meant
to make some of
> 2的额外除法只是为了使一些
our later calculations
look neater,
> 我们后来的计算看起来更整洁，
but the cost function
still works whether you
> 但成本函数仍然有效，无论你
include this division
by 2 or not.
> 包括这个除以2的除法还是不包括。
This expression right here is
> 这里的表达式是
the cost function and
we're going to write
> 成本函数，我们将写
J of wb to refer to
the cost function.
> J of wb来指代成本函数。
This is also called the
squared error cost function,
> 这也被称为平方误差成本函数，
and it's called this
because you're taking
> 这样称呼是因为你正在
the square of these error terms.
> 这些错误项的平方。
In machine learning
different people
> 在机器学习中，不同的人
will use different
cost functions
> 将使用不同的成本函数
for different applications,
> 用于不同的应用，
but the squared error cost
function is by far the most
> 但平方误差成本函数是迄今为止最常用的
commonly used one for
> 用于
linear regression
and for that matter,
> 线性回归和此外，
for all regression
problems where it
> 对于所有回归问题，它
seems to give good results
for many applications.
> 似乎为许多应用提供了良好的结果。
Just as a reminder,
the prediction y hat
> 只是作为提醒，预测y hat
is equal to the outputs
of the model f at x.
> 等于模型f在x处的输出。
We can rewrite the
cost function J of
> 我们可以重写成本函数J of
wb as 1 over 2m times
> wb为1除以2m乘以
the sum from i
equals 1 to m of f
> 从i等于1到m的f的总和
of x^i minus y^i the
quantity squared.
> x^i减y^i的数量平方。
Eventually we're going to
want to find values of
> 最终，我们将要找到
w and b that make the
cost function small.
> 使成本函数变小的w和b的值。
But before going there,
> 但在那之前，
let's first gain more
intuition about what
> 让我们首先更多地了解
J of wb is really computing.
> J of wb真正计算的是什么。
At this point you might
be thinking we've done
> 此时，你可能会认为我们已经完成了
a whole lot of math to
define the cost function.
> 定义成本函数的大量数学。
But what exactly is it doing?
> 但它到底在做什么？
Let's go on to the next
video where we'll step
> 让我们继续下一个视频，我们将迈出
through one example of
what the cost function
> 通过一个例子，成本函数
is really computing
that I hope will
> 真正计算的是我希望
help you build
intuition about what it
> 帮助你建立直觉，它
means if J of wb is large
versus if the cost j is small.
> 如果J of wb很大，与成本j很小相比。
Let's go on to the next video.
> 让我们继续下一个视频。